http://www.fyc.org.uk/legal

Members
Data Protection and General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR)FYC takes the management and security of personal information seriously and has appropriate controls in place to ensure it remains secure.  Our Data Protection and Retention Policy and our Privacy Statements have been reviewed in light of GDPR.  These can be found below:FYC Data Protection and Retention PolicyFYC Privacy Statement for New MembersFYC Privacy Statement for Existing MembersFYC Privacy Statement for Staff and VolunteersSAFEGUARDINGThe FYC Safeguarding Policy is reviewed annually and shared with all staff, volunteers and FYC parents. The policy can be found here:FYC Safeguarding Policy June 2020LegalThe content of this website is copyright © Farnham Youth Choir.All rights expressly reserved. All third-party trademarks and copyrights on this site are acknowledged.The images on this website are not in the public domain. They are the sole property of the copyright holders. These images may not be copied, downloaded, saved locally, reproduced on the internet, redistributed, sold, altered, enhanced, modified by artificial, digital or computer imaging or in any other form without the express written permission of the copyright holder. Please contact FYC for details.Farnham Youth Choir is not responsible for the content of external sites to which this site may link.Farnham Youth Choir is a participant in the Amazon EU Associates Programme, an affiliate advertising programme designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.co.uk.Farnham Youth Choir is a registered charity in England and Wales (1145358).
